Direct from the heart
Spielberg is a documentary film directed by Susan Lacy.
A documentary on the life and career of one of the most
influential film directors of all time, Steven Spielberg.
Self, played by Steven Spielberg.
Self, played by Martin Scorsese.
Self, played by Richard Dreyfuss.
Self, played by Francis Ford Coppola.
Self, played by Tom Hanks.
Self, played by J.J. Abrams.
Spielberg is a 2017 American documentary film directed by Susan Lacy, and is
centered on the career of film director Steven Spielberg.
It premiered at the 2017 New York Film Festival and
aired on HBO on October 7, 2017.
The documentary chronicles Spielberg's career, including
interviews with collaborators, family and friends.
Some of the events explored, particularly of his early life, would go on to be
dramatized in Spielberg's 2022 semi-autobiographical film The Fabelmans.
The film explores themes of movie business, biography, archive
footage, hollywood star, celebrity interview.